http://tenstep.com/privacy-policy/

TenStep Privacy Policy
At TenStep, we are dedicated to preserving the privacy of all of our customers.  TenStep recognizes that our customers have valid concerns about how the personal information that they submit online will be used, and TenStep pledges to provide the safest online environment possible.
Read below to find out how TenStep’s commitment to privacy benefits you.
Non-Members That Are Browsing Our Content
Some of the content found on our websites is available for anyone to read at their leisure. TenStep does not collect personal information from customers who are simply visiting one of our websites. TenStep does not use cookies, so users remain completely anonymous. If you visited our website by clicking on a link from one of our affiliates, it is possible a cookie was placed on your machine by the affiliate tracking software. The only purpose of this cookie is to note that you were referred to us by an affiliate so that the affiliate can receive a commission payment if you buy something.
TenStep Members
Much of our content can be viewed by people that register with us as “Members”. Visitors are not required to become registered Members, but we do offer incentives to register and we request a minimum amount of information. There is no cost to register as a Member. Your registration information is stored in a secure database for use by TenStep only. Your personal information will never be shared with or sold to a third party. Members will automatically be signed up to receive our weekly Tip-of-the-Week newsletter. Each newsletter will contain a link to unsubscribe at any time.
People That Have Requested Information from TenStep
When you request information from TenStep about our products or services, you must release a minimal amount of information (such as name, email address, etc.).  This information, along with your original request, is stored in a secure database for use by TenStep only. Your personal information will never be shared with or sold to a third party.
TenStep occasionally sends out emails with special announcements, offers, or updates. If you would prefer not to receive these emails, you can unsubscribe at any time.
Customers That Have Made a Purchase from TenStep
When you make purchase a product or service from TenStep, you must release a minimal amount of information (such as name, email address, postal address, etc.).  This information is stored in a secure database for use by TenStep only.  A portion of this information is also made available to our global offices. Your personal information will never be shared with or sold to other third parties.
TenStep maintains this information for a number of purposes.
In the event that a TenStep customer loses his or her username and/or password (where applicable), we will use our database to verify that customer’s purchase and retrieve his or her information.
TenStep occasionally sends out emails with special announcements, offers, or updates.  If you would prefer not to receive these emails, you can send an email to admin@tenstep.com requesting to have your name removed from our mailing list.
TenStep will also send an email before your license is due to expire to tell you how much you will owe to renew your license (where applicable).
TenStep understands that our customers are concerned about the privacy of their credit card information when making purchases online.  For that reason, TenStep uses a secure third-party credit card processing site.  The information you provide on this site will remain strictly confidential and will not be used for any unauthorized purpose.  It will not be shared with any third parties.
TenStep realizes that some of our customers are uncomfortable entering credit card information online.  To better serve the needs of all of our customers, TenStep also accepts checks. Customers may also call TenStep to make a credit card purchase by phone.
Other
TenStep sends out a weekly email entitled “Project Management Tip of the Week.”  This email is only sent to individuals that sign up to receive the email, and individuals that register as “Members”.  This email list will not be sold to or shared with any third parties.  You may remove your name from this list at any time by clicking on a link at the bottom of the email (this link appears every week) or by emailing your request to admin@tenstep.com.
TenStep websites contain some links to third-party sites.  TenStep has no control over these sites.  These sites have their own privacy policies and customers who visit these sites should become familiar with them.
TenStep values our customers and takes the privacy concerns of our customers seriously.  If you have any further questions regarding TenStep’s privacy policy, please contact us:
Email – admin@tenstep.com
Phone – 1-877-536-8434
(770) 795-9097
Product info: project management, portfolio management, project office, PMO, risk management, project lifecycle management, project consulting, methodology development, quality management, project management training, PMP Exam Prep
TenStep, Inc. 30 Chatham Rd, #388, Short Hills, NJ 07078 Phone: 877.536.8434 or 404.375.5862
Scroll to top
